♪ I'M GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA HAVE MYSELF
A TIME ♪
♪ FRIENDLY FACES
EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ HUMBLE FOLKS
WITHOUT TEMPTATION ♪
♪ GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA LEAVE
MY WOE'S BEHIND ♪
♪ AMPLE PARKING
DAY OR NIGHT ♪
♪ PEOPLE SPOUTING
"HOWDY NEIGHBOR" ♪
♪ HEADED ON
UP TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA SEE IF
I CAN'T UNWIND ♪
( mumbling )
♪ SO COME ON DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ AND MEET SOME
FRIENDS OF MINE ♪
NOW YOU
BE CAREFUL ERIC.
THE WOODS CAN BE
VERY DANGEROUS.
OKAY MOM.
READY TO GO
HUNTING CARTMAN?
MY UNCLE JIMBO SAYS WE GOTTA
GET UP THERE EARLY.
RIGHT
UNCLE JIMBO?
THAT'S RIGHT
STANLY.
ANIMALS ARE MUCH EASIER
TO SHOOT IN THE MORNING.
HERE HON,
I PACKED YOU CHEESY POOFS
AND HAPPY TARTS.
DON'T WORRY
MISS CARTMAN,
WE'LL TAKE
GOOD CARE OF HIM.
I BROUGHT MY OLD WAR BUDDY DAN
TO KEEP THINGS SAFE.
( voice box )
HELLO MRS. CARTMAN,
HOW ARE YOU TODAY?
BE SURE TO USE
LOTS OF BUG SPRAY,
AND IF YOU HAVE
TO POO-POO
DON'T WIPE
WITH POISON IVY.
( laughing )
DUDE,
THAT'S SICK MOM!
I KNOW IT CAN GET SCARY
UP IN THOSE THOSE WOODS.
BUT JUST REMEMBER,
MOMMY'S NOT
FAR AWAY.
( laughing )
DRIVE, DRIVE!
YOU GIVE YOUR
MOMMY A KISSY.
DRIVE THE CAR, DAMMIT,
DRIVE!
DON'T GET SCARED UP IN
THE MOUNTAINS, CARTMAN.
SHUT UP, I'M NOT
SCARED OF NOTHING!
MAYBE YOUR MOM CAN GIVE ME
A KISS TOO, CARTMAN.
( mumbling )
WHOA!
THAT'S DISGUSTING!
YOU PIECE OF CRAP,
I'LL KILL YOU!
THAT'S THE
SPIRIT BOYS!
LET'S GET THAT
TESTOSTERONE FLOWING!
NOW BOYS,
I NEED TO GET SERIOUS
FOR A MINUTE.
I WANT YOU TO UNDERSTAND
A FEW BASIC RULES OF HUNTING,
SINCE THIS IS
YOUR FIRST TIME.
FIRST OF ALL, DON'T EVER
WALK WITH YOUR GUN
UNLESS THE
SAFETY IS ON.
SECOND, DON'T SHOOT ANYTHING
THAT LOOKS HUMAN.
AND THIRD, NEVER SPILL YOUR BEER
IN THE BULLET CHAMBER.
( Stan )
UNCLE JIMBO,
WE DON'T DRINK BEER.
YOU WHAT?!
( voice box )
OH, YEAH,
THAT'S RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK
8-YEAR-OLD KIDS DRINK BEER.
I LIKE
CHOCOLATE MILK!
WE'LL BE DOING PLENTY
OF DRINKING ON THIS TRIP.
AFTER ALL,
HUNTING SOBER IS LIKE...
FISHING...
SOBER.
IT SURE WILL BE NICE TO GET OUT
OF THE CITY FOR A WHILE.
AWAY FROM
CIVILIZATION.
WELL,
HERE WE ARE.
OKAY, EACH OF YOU
YOUNG 'UN'S TAKE A GUN,
A BEER
AND SOME SMOKES.
HEY, I DIDN'T
GET A GUN!
SWEET.
THIS IS LIKE THE GUN
I USED IN 'NAM.
YOU WEREN'T
IN VIETNAM CARTMAN.
( voice box )
WERE YOU STATIONED
IN DA NANG?
CARTMAN ALWAYS
MAKES STUFF UP.
YOU CAN'T BELIEVE
ANYTHING HE SAYS.
HEY, I'LL BLOW
YOUR FREAKING HEAD OFF!
LOOK OUT SON,
THAT'S DANGEROUS!
YOU'RE GONNA
SPILL YOUR BEER.
MY UNCLE JIMBO SAYS
THAT AFTER THIS
HE'S GONNA TAKE ME
HUNTING IN AFRICA.
WOW,
THAT'LL BE COOL!
MY MOM SAYS THERE'S A LOT OF
BLACK PEOPLE IN AFRICA.
BOYS,
LOOKIE THERE.
THAT THERE IS A
ROCKY MOUNTAIN BLACK BEAR.
ONE OF THE FEW REMAINING
OF ITS KIND.
ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
MY GOD, IT'S COMING
RIGHT FOR US!
HEY, IT WASN'T
COMING RIGHT FOR US.
IT WAS JUST
SITTING THERE.
SHH,
NOT SO LOUD.
THAT THERE IS JUST
A TECHNICALITY.
WHAT DO
YOU MEAN?
YOU SEE, THE DEMOCRATS
HAVE PASSED A LOT OF LAWS
TRYING TO STOP US
FROM HUNTING.
DEMOCRATS
PISS ME OFF.
THEY SAY WE CAN'T SHOOT
CERTAIN ANIMALS ANYMORE
UNLESS THEY'RE POSING
AN IMMEDIATE THREAT.
THEREFORE, BEFORE
WE SHOOT SOMETHING
WE HAVE TO SAY
"IT'S COMING RIGHT FOR US".
WOW, YOU'RE SMART
UNCLE JIMBO.
JIMBO, LOOK.
OH, IT'S A DEER.
LOOKS LIKE ABOUT
A 46-GAUGE, NED.
IT'S COMING
RIGHT FOR US!
KICK ASS!
DID YOU
SEE THAT?
I WAS IMPALED BY THAT
FEROCIOUS CHARGING BUCK.
RABBIT, RABBIT
FIVE O'CLOCK.
LET'S MOVE!
MOVE!
IS THIS HUNTING?
I GUESS SO.
DUDE, I'M STARTING
TO HAVE FLASHBACKS.
WHAT?
STAND FORTH,
PULL UP FLANK!
LOOK OUT FOR CHARLIES
UP IN THE TREES!
THIS ONE'S
YOURS STAN.
IT'S COMING
RIGHT FOR US!
RIGHT FOR US.
SHOOT IT STAN.
I GOT YOUR BACK
SOLDIER.
I CAN'T.
WHAT THE--
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
I DON'T WANNA
SHOOT THE BUNNY.
WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT
YOU'RE BABBLING,
YOU'RE NOT MAKING ANY SENSE.
YOU'RE HYSTERICAL!
I'M NOT
HYSTERICAL,
I JUST DON'T WANNA
SHOOT THE BUNNY.
NO NEPHEW OF MINE IS
GONNA BE A TREE-HUGGER!
YEAH, HIPPIE!
GO BACK TO WOODSTOCK
IF YOU CAN'T SHOOT ANYTHING.
I CAN SHOOT YOU,
FAT ASS!
I CAN
SHOOT YOU TOO!
I'LL KILL YOU!
I'LL FILL YOU
FULL OF LEAD!
( rumbling )
HEY WHAT'S THAT?
( humming )
( rumbling sounds )
WHAT THE HECK
IS THIS?
YEAH FRANK?
IT'S RANDY.
GOOD.
YEAH, LISTEN,
THE LITTLE NEEDLE'S MOVING.
IT'S GOING BACK AND FORTH
REALLY FAST.
WHAT DOES
THAT MEAN?
UH-HUH.
LET ME CHECK.
YEAH,
IT'S SMOKING.
UH-HUH.
OH, REALLY?
REALLY?
OH, MY GOD!
A VOLCANO!
( suspenseful music )
( sipping )
EHHHH.
MY WEENIES
WON'T COOK.
THIS WOOD
WON'T BURN.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL HAVE TO USE
THE OLD INDIAN FIRE TRICK.
YEAH.
( laughing )
HEY STOP, DROP,
AND ROLL, NED!
WHOA!
GODDAMNIT,
I JUST GOT THAT VAN.
HOW THE HELL ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO GET HOME?
OH, IT HURTS,
IT HURTS!
HEY, YOU GUYS,
THIS ONE'S PRETTY
GOOD RIGHT NOW.
BUT YOU SEE
MR. MAYOR,
YOU CAN'T STOP SERVING SALISBURY
STEAK IN OUR PUBLIC SCHOOLS.
WHAT'S NEXT,
MEAT LOAF?
WE ARE QUITE AWARE
OF YOUR CONCERNS CHEF, BUT--
( intercom )
Mayor, the geologist
is here to see you.
MY GEOLOGIST...?
NOW?
TELL HIM THE
INFECTION IS FINE
AND I DON'T NEED
ANOTHER CHECK-UP.
No Mayor, that's
a gynecologist,
a geologist
studies the Earth.
DON'T YOU THINK
I KNOW THAT?
HOW DEAR YOU INSULT
MY INTELLECT!
I WENT TO PRINCETON
FOR GODSAKE!
YOU GET OUT
OF MY OFFICE!
I'm not in
your office Mayor,
I'm talking to you
through a speaker.
JUST SEND IN
THE GEOMETRIST!
Geologist.
YOU ARE
FIRED, BUDDY!
Thank you Mayor, it's been
great working for you.
MAYOR, WE HAVE GOT
A VERY BIG PROBLEM.
MT. EVANSON
IS ABOUT TO ERUPT.
( suspense music )
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN
TO THE TOWN?
THIS GRAPH SHOWS EVERYTHING
FROM "NORMAL" TO "BAD".
RIGHT NOW SOUTH PARK
IS HERE.
( suspense music )
MY GOD!
MAYOR, SOME OF
THE SCHOOL CHILDREN
ARE UP CAMPING ON THAT
MOUNTAIN RIGHT NOW!
THIS IS BIG.
JOHNSON, JOHNSON,
ARE YOU THERE?!
( intercom )
You just fired Johnson,
Mayor.
I'm his
replacement, Ted.
TED, WE HAVE GOT
A MAJOR CRISIS HERE!
I WANT YOU TO GET ON THE PHONE
AND CALL "INSIDE EDITION",
"RESCUE 911"
AND "ENTERTAINMENT TONIGHT".
YOU BETTER GET MY STYLIST
ON THE PHONE TOO.
DON'T WORRY,
THINGS ARE UNDER CONTROL.
AND THEN NED PICKED UP
THE GRENADE
AND BOOM!
BLASTED HIS
ARM CLEAR OFF!
WE SPENT THREE HOURS LOOKING
FOR THAT DAMN ARM,
BUT IT WAS
NEVER TO BE FOUND.
SOME SAY IT'S STILL
CRAWLING AROUND TO THIS DAY.
RAAHH...!
GOTCHA!
THAT'S NOT
SCARY.
YOU WERE SCARED CARTMAN,
YOU ALMOST PEED YOUR PANTS.
SHUT UP I DIDN'T
PEE MY PANTS!
HEY NED,
HAND ME THAT GIN.
YOU BOYS
WANNA TIE ONE ON?
NO, THANKS, THAT STUFF
TASTES LIKE PEE.
YEAH,
CARTMAN'S PEE.
YOU WOULD
TASTE MY PEE!
WHAT THE HELL'S
WRONG WITH YOU?
CAN'T YOU HAVE
A LITTLE ALCOHOL?
CHRIST, LOOK AT THAT
LITTLE BASTARD GO!
YOU SEE THAT STAN?
NOW THAT IS A DIRTY
LITTLE BASTARD.
HEY, I'M A DIRTY
LITTLE BASTARD TOO.
HEY YOU GUYS,
I KNOW A SCARY STORY.
SHUT UP CARTMAN,
YOU CAN'T SCARE ANYBODY.
OH YEAH?
HAVE YOU GUYS EVER
HEARD OF SKUZZLE-BUTT?
WHAT BUTT?
SKUZZLE-BUTT
IS A CREATURE
THAT LIVES UP
ON THIS VERY MOUNTAIN
AND KILLS ANYBODY
WHO CLIMBS TO THE TOP.
WHY?
BECAUSE IT LOVES
THE TASTE OF BLOOD
AND LIKES TO ADD PIECES
TO ITS DEFORMED BODY.
DEFORMED HOW?
WELL, ON HIS LEFT ARM,
INSTEAD OF A HAND,
HE HAS...
A HOOK.
A KNIFE.
NO, A PIECE
OF CELERY.
CELERY?
YES, AND HE WALKS
WITH A LIMP
BECAUSE ONE OF
HIS LEGS IS MISSING.
AND WHERE HIS LEG
SHOULD BE
THERE'S NOTHING BUT...
PATRICK DUFFY.
PATRICK DUFFY?
DAMNIT CARTMAN,
THAT'S NOT SCARY?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
"STEP BY STEP"?
SO HE LIVES ALONE
ON THIS MOUNTAIN
AND WEAVES BASKETS
AND OTHER ASSORTED CRAFTS.
THEY SAY THAT
ON QUIET NIGHTS
YOU CAN HEAR HIM
WEAVING HIS BASKETS.
( weaving sounds )
CARTMAN, YOU SUCK AT
TELLING SCARY STORIES!
YEAH GIVE ME
THAT FLASHLIGHT.
( rumbling )
WHAT IS THAT?
MAYBE IT'S SKUZZLE-BUTT
COMING TO WEAVE US
INTO BASKETS.
HEY,
IT MIGHT BE!
GOSH, I HOPE HE DOESN'T CUT ME
WITH HIS CELERY HAND.
SCREW YOU GUYS!
GO TO HELL!
NED, WHY DON'T YOU WHIP OUT
THE OLD CANCER KAZOO?
LET'S DO
A LITTLE SONG.
( voice box )
♪ COOMBAYA,
MY LORD ♪
♪ COOMBAYA ♪
♪ COOMBAYA,
MY LORD ♪
♪ COOMBAYA ♪
♪ COOMBAYA,
MY LORD ♪
♪ COOMBAYA ♪
♪ OH, LORD
COOMBAYA ♪
♪ SOMEONE'S CRYING, LORD ♪
♪ COOMBAYA ♪
THEY DON'T THINK
SKUZZLE-BUTT IS SCARY, HUH?
LET'S SEE
HOW THEY LIKE IT
WHEN THEY ACTUALLY
SEE SKUZZLE-BUTT.
I'LL SCARE THE HELL
OUT OF 'EM TOMORROW.
♪ SOMEONE'S CRYING LORD,
COOMBAYA ♪
♪ OH, LORD,
STAN, STAN,
WAKE UP!
WHAT DUDE?
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE CARTMAN IS.
I THINK SOMETHING
TOOK HIM AWAY.
WHERE'S MY UNCLE JIMBO
AND NED?
THEY'RE OUT FISHING
WITH KENNY.
BUT THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
MY CAMPING TRIP.
WHY DO THEY LIKE
KENNY SO MUCH?
DOESN'T HE LIKE ME
ANYMORE?
WELL STAN, YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT I THINK?
WHAT?
( farting )
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL MORNING
FOR FISHING.
THERE'S ONE,
THERE'S A FISH RIGHT THERE!
GOT IT.
GREAT INSTINCTS BOY.
UNCLE JIMBO,
CARTMAN'S MISSING!
WHO?
THE FAT KID?
YEAH.
I GUESS WE BETTER
GO LOOK FOR HIM.
NED, WE GOTTA
CUT IT SHORT.
FIRE UP THE 12-20!
WELL I THINK
THAT'S ABOUT THE LIMIT
FOR OUR
FISHING PERMIT.
IT SMELLS LIKE
DEAD FISH HERE.
( mumbling )
OH, MAN,
THAT IS NASTY.
I DON'T THINK
I'VE EVER SEEN
A KID AS COOL
AS YOU KENNY.
I'M MAKING YOU
MY HONORARY NEPHEW.
BUT NOW A TICKING
TIME BOMB OF HOT LAVA
WAITS TO
ENGULF THESE PEOPLE
AND END THEIR MISERABLE LIVES
WITH ONE LAST FLEETING MOMENT
OF EXCRUCIATINGLY
PAINFUL BURNING AGONY.
HEY, I'M ON TV!
I'M ON TV!
MAYOR, WHAT YOU DOING
TO PREPARE FOR THIS
INEVITABLE
CATASTROPHE?
ALL WE KNOW
RIGHT NOW
IS THAT SOME OF
OUR CHILDREN
ARE CAMPING ON
THAT MOUNTAIN--
I'M SORRY,
CAN I START OVER?
HUH?
YOU CAN
EDIT THIS, RIGHT?
READY,
THREE, TWO, ONE.
ALL WE KNOW
RIGHT NOW
IS SOME OF OUR CHILDREN ARE
UP CAMPING ON THAT MOUNTAIN.
WE CAN'T DO ANYTHING
UNTIL WE GET THEM!
OKAY PEOPLE,
LET'S GO GET THOSE KIDS!
C'MON EVERYBODY, YOU GOTTA
HELP THE CHILDREN.
HE COULDN'T
HAVE GONE FAR...
UNLESS SOMETHING
DRUG HIM OFF.
THERE'S NOT MANY ANIMALS
OUT TODAY JIMBO.
YEAH, IT'S ALMOST LIKE
SOMETHING FUNNY'S GOING ON.
( rumbling )
CHRIST NED, WHAT'D YOU
HAVE FOR BREAKFAST?
I DON'T KNOW MAN,
I'VE GOT SOME BAD GAS.
WAIT,
THERE'S A RAM!
IT'S COMING
RIGHT FOR US!
( gunshots )
NICE SHOOTING,
KENNY.
HERE, YOU NEED
A BIGGER GUN.
LOOK!
I AM SKUZZLE-BUTT,
LORD OF THE MOUNTAINS!
BEHOLD MY
PATRICK DUFFY LEG!
WHAT IS IT?
DUDE, IT'S
SKUZZLE-BUTT!
CARTMAN
WASN'T LYING.
HOLY CROW!
WE CAN MAKE A MINT
KILLING THIS THING.
WE'LL BE ON THE COVER
OF "GUNS AND AMMO".
THIS CALLS
FOR SOME HJ-14.
THOSE GUYS
ARE TOTALLY SCARED.
FIRE IN THE HOLE!
HOLY CRAP!
DAMN, I THINK
I MISSED.
WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG
WITH YOU PEOPLE?!
C'MON, LET'S MOVE!
MOVE!
WAIT, WAIT!
IS IT ON?
OKAY.
OKAY, PEOPLE, FORM GROUPS
AND SEARCH THE MOUNTAIN.
REPORT BACK HERE EVERY HOUR,
YOU GOT THAT?
MAYOR, I MIGHT
HAVE AN IDEA.
OH, WHAT?
IF WE CAN DIG
A VERY LARGE TRENCH
WE CAN DIVERT THE LAVA
INTO A CANYON.
THEN IT WOULD
BYPASS SOUTH PARK
PRETTY MUCH
COMPLETELY.
AND... THAT WOULD
BE GOOD, RIGHT?
I'M PRETTY SURE.
WELL, WHAT ARE
WE WAITING FOR?
OKAY, PEOPLE,
CHANGE OF PLANS.
HALF OF YOU
GRAB SHOVELS.
THESE LOOK LIKE
HIS TRACKS.
HE MUST'VE
GONE THIS WAY.
NED, PREPARE
SOME HK-12.
I'LL BET THAT SUCKER'S HEADED
FOR A HIGHER ELEVATION.
THE HIGHER--
BIRD!
THE HIGHER UP IT GOES
THE BETTER IT CAN BREATHE.
LOOK,
UP THERE!
YOU GUYS,
IT'S JUST ME!
ARE WE SURE
IT'S SKUZZLE-BUTT?
DOES IT HAVE PATRICK DUFFY
FOR A LEG?
I CAN'T TELL,
LET'S KILL IT!
I GOTTA GET OUT OF THIS
STUPID COSTUME!
KENNY,
YOU TAKE THE FRONT.
NO, I CAN DO IT,
UNCLE JIMBO.
I WANNA
BAG THAT ANIMAL.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT, KIDDO!
LET'S HUNT!
YOU GUYS, YOU GUYS,
I WAS JUST KIDDING!
( reporter )
AS SOME PEOPLE OF SOUTH PARK
TRY DESPERATELY
TO SAVE
THEIR MOUNTAIN TOWN,
OTHERS LOOK FOR
THE MISSING TOWNSPEOPLE.
BUT ALL MUST TAKE
EVERY PRECAUTION NECESSARY.
OKAY, PEOPLE,
LISTEN UP.
AS WE NEAR THE TOP
OF THE MOUNTAIN
THE CHANCES OF OUR ENCOUNTERING
SOME LAVA BECOMES GREAT.
THEREFORE I HAVE SPECIAL
ORDERED THIS TRAINING FILM
TO ASSIST US
IN VOLCANO SAFETY.
MR. GARRISON,
IF YOU WOULD PLEASE.
Harborers of sorrow,
Natural disasters
can be the cause
of troubling and
undesirable stress,
and a volcano
is no exception.
But what should you do
if a volcano erupts
near you
or your family?
Here we see the Stevens' family
enjoying a picnic,
But suddenly daughter
hears a noise...
It's a volcano.
Junior seems worried,
but have no fear Junior,
Jane learned in school
what to do
when you hear
a volcano erupt.
That's right, Jane,
duck and cover.
So what will you do when
you hear a volcano erupting?
That's right,
duck and cover.
Looks like
you got the idea.
Thank you
and goodbye.
OKAY,
ANY QUESTIONS?
THAT HAS
GOT TO BE
THE MOST RIDICULOUS
LOAD OF PIG CRAP
I HAVE EVER SEEN!
THAT'S ENOUGH
OUT OF YOU!
I'M GONNA BAG
SKUZZLE-BUTT,
THEN WE'LL SEE
WHO'S A LITTLE BASTARD.
( Cartman )
HEY SERIOUSLY,
YOU GUYS!
KILL IT STAN,
KILL IT.
C'MON, STAN,
KILL IT!
GODDAMNIT,
I CAN'T DO IT!
YOU PANSY,
GIVE ME THAT GUN!
CARTMAN?
GODDAMNIT,
DON'T SHOOT ME!
WHAT THE
SAM HELL?
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO SCARE YOU GUYS.
YOU CAN PUT
THE GUNS DOWN NOW!
SO MUCH FOR THE COVER
OF "GUNS AND AMMO".
BUT I THINK WE'VE LEARNED
SOME IMPORTANT LESSONS.
I THINK--
( Stan )
WHOA!
HOLY CRAP.
THE MOUNTAIN,
ITS BLOWN ITS TOP!
OH, MY GOD,
THEY KILLED KENNY!
( mumbling )
LOOK,
THE VOLCANO!
WAIT,
DUCK AND COVER!
( screaming )
THAT LAVA'S COMING
RIGHT FOR US!
OH, NO,
LOOK!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS
TRENCH DOING HERE?!
WE CAN'T
GET ACROSS!
IT NOW LOOKS AS IF
THE MISSING CHILDREN
ARE TRAPPED IN THE PATH
OF HOT NASTY LAVA.
GOD, PLEASE DELIVER THOSE
DARLING KIDS FROM--
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT,
THREE, TWO, AND ONE.
GOD, PLEASE DELIVER...
HELP!
JIMINY!
IT'S THE REAL
SKUZZLE-BUTT!
WHAT?!
SKUZZLE-BUTT'S REAL?
OH, MY GOD,
LOOK AT HIS LEG!
HI KIDS, I'M TV's
PATRICK DUFFY.
QUICK, NED,
SHOOT IT!
OH, NO,
OUT OF AMMO.
WHAT IS
THAT THING?
THAT'S SKUZZLE-BUTT.
HE HAS PATRICK DUFFY FOR A LEG
AND WEAVES BASKETS.
THIS ISN'T
HAPPENING.
EVERYONE
LOOK AWAY PLEASE!
NOTHING
TO SEE HERE.
WELL BOYS,
I'M SORRY I GOT YOU
ALL KILLED.
AAH...!
( Stan )
WHOA, HE BUILT
A WICKER BASKET.
HEY,
HE'S SAVING US!
SKUZZLE-BUTT
SAVED THE DAY.
AND MY
CALCULATIONS WORKED.
THE LAVA'S FOLLOWING
THE TRENCH INTO THE CANYON.
WHERE EXACTLY
DOES THE CANYON GO?
UH...
( crowd screaming )
SOUTH PARK
IS SAVED!
( Stan )
HEY LOOK,
KENNY'S OKAY!
AND NOW THESE HUMBLE PEOPLE
CAN REJOICE AND CELEBRATE
THEIR JOVIAL VICTORY
OVER NATURE.
I'M GETTING WORD THAT THE CHEF
OF THE SCHOOL CAFETERIA
WANTS TO
SING A SONG
ABOUT THIS THRILLING
STRUGGLE OF HUMANITY.
♪ MMM BABY,
EVERY TIME THAT WE KISS ♪
♪ HOT LAVA ♪
♪ EVERY TIME WE MAKE LOVE
THERE'S LAVA ♪
♪ HOT LAVA ♪
♪ LAVA SO HOT
IT MAKES ME SWEAT ♪
♪ LAVA SO WARM
AND RED AND WET ♪
♪ LAVA ♪
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY
ABOUT THIS WONDERFUL OUTCOME?
WE OWE EVERYTHING
TO THIS FRIENDLY
YET MISUNDERSTOOD
CREATURE.
THANK YOU
SKUZZLE-BUTT.
FRIEND.
OH, HOW SWEET.
I DID IT,
I DID IT!
I FINALLY
KILLED SOMETHING.
OH, MY GOD,
WHAT HAS HE DONE?
TURN OFF
THE CAMERAS!
HEY,
THAT WAS EASY.
NO!
WHY GOD, WHY?!
DAMNIT STAN, YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE DONE THAT!
WHY?
MAKE UP
YOUR MIND.
STAN, SOME THINGS
YOU KILL
AND SOME THINGS
YOU DON'T, SEE?
NO.
ONLY NOW
IN THIS LATE HOUR
DO I SEE
THE FOLLY OF GUNS.
I'LL NEVER USE
A GUN AGAIN.
( gun goes off )
BUT I JUST WANTED YOU
TO BE PROUD OF ME
LIKE YOU WERE
WITH KENNY.
BUT KENNY'S
DEAD NOW STAN
AND YOU'RE ALWAYS
GONNA BE MY NEPHEW.
AND YOU JUST CAN'T
KILL ANYTHING.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
DUDE, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HUNTING AT ALL.
YEAH, IT'S STUPID,
LET'S GO WATCH CARTOONS.
YEAH, CARTOONS
KICK ASS.